Richard York Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artists' Artwork Files, circa 1865-2004, Series 2:; (Boxes 7-64; 56.85 linear feet)
  - General, circa 1865-2004, 2.1:
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 414aCY: The Green Calash, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 414bCY: The Green Calash, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 416CY: A Woman From Normandy, circa 1981 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 417CY: First Night in Venice, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 418CY: City Garden, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 419CY: Cabin in the Woods, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 420CY: Jerusalem Domes With Color, 1936, circa 1981 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 422CY: The Willow Whistle, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 422bCY: The Willow Whistle, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 423CY: The Vegetable Cart, circa 1910-1940, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 424LY: Lady With a Fan, circa 1940, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 434CY: Swill-cart, circa 1981 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 435CY: Amsterdam, circa 1981 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 436CY: Albany Street, Boston, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 437CY: Garden Party by Jamaica Pond, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 438CY: Portrait of a Lady, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 446CY: Tranquility, circa 1981 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 451CY: St. James Parish, Louisiana, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 452CY: Belmont, Louisiana, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 65)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 453CY: Pecan Trees, Charleston, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 66)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 472CY: At the Edge of a Pond #2, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 67)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 473CY: Spring Harvest in the Snow, Ohio, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 68)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 474CY: The Begger, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 69)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 475CY: Woman Seated in a Doorway, Holland, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 70)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 476CY: Twilight in the Park, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 71)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 478CY: Dives Market, Calvados, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 479CY: Seated Woman, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 73)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 485CY: Landscape With Purple Flowers, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 74)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 532CY: An Old Garden, Newport, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 75)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 545CY: Landscape With Blue Flowers, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 76)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 552CY: Robby, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 77)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 1253CY: Street at Mont St. Michel, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 78)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 1323CY: Study of Roses, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 79)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 1324CY: Haying Scene, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 80)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 1325CY: Pines by Salt Meadow, 1984-1985, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 81)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 1326CY: Coquelicots, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 82)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 1904CY: View at Folly Cove, Rockport, 1981, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 83)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 1999JY: Study of Roses, 1987-1989 (Box 24, Folder 84)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 2465RY: View at Folly Cove, Rockport, Massachusetts, The Artist's Garden, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 85)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 4814CY: The Vegetable Cart, Charleston, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 86)
    - Hale, Ellen Day, 6042CY: Still Life, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 87)
    - Hale, Lilian Westcott, 454CY: Palm Trees, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 88)
    - Hale, Lilian Westcott, 455CY: Hibiscus, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 89)
    - Hale, Lilian Westcott, 456CY: Apple Blossoms (smaller version), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 90)
    - Hale, Lilian Westcott, 457CY: Apple Blossoms (larger version), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 91)
    - Hale, Lilian Westcott, 458CY: Birds in a Tree, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 92)
    - Hale, Lilian Westcott, 466CY: Margaret Williams, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 93)
    - Hale, Lilian Westcott, 467CY: The Samovar, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 94)
    - Hale, Lilian Westcott, 468CY: Perdita, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 95)
    - Hale, Lilian Westcott, 2896CY: Japonoiserie, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 96)
    - Hale, Lilian Westcott, 6100RY: On Christmas Day in the Morning (The Wreath), 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 97)
    - Hale, Philip Leslie, 4216CY: The Rub Down, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 98)
    - Hale, Philip Leslie, 8173CY: Lady With a Fan, 2001-2004 (Box 24, Folder 99)
    - Hale, Susan, 513CY: Near Dorking, England, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 100)
    - Hall, George Henry, 616CY: Girl With Kittens, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 101)
    - Hall, George Henry, 692CY: Still Life With Grapes, Peaches and Cherries, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 102)
    - Hall, George Henry, 3898RY: Grapes in a Basket, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 103)
    - Hall, George Henry, 4011CY: Pomegranates, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 104)
    - Hall, May Whitney, 1095RY: Thistles, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 105)
    - Hallett, Hendricks A., 3299CY: Marblehead Harbor, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 106)
    - Halpert, Samuel, 3379CY: Interior (The Dressmaker), 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 107)
    - Halpert, Samuel, 6907CY: The Pont Neuf, Paris, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 108)
    - Halpert, Samuel, 7444CY: Smokestack and Steeples on the Harbor, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 109)
    - Hamilton, Easter Field, 3236CY: Brooklyn, 1903, 1991, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 110)
    - Hamilton, Easter Field, 3237CY: Brooklyn, 1991, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 111)
    - Hamilton, Easter Field, 4622LY: Brooklyn Waterfront, circa 1995 (Box 24, Folder 112)
    - Hamilton, Easter Field, 4717LY: Brooklyn, 1903, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 113)
    - Hamilton, Easter Field, 4718CY: Brooklyn Waterfront, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 114)
    - Hamilton, Edward Wilbur Dean, 7055CY: Houses on a Snowy River Bank, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 115)
    - Hamilton, James, 2517LY: A Wreck on the Coast of Wales, Evening, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 116)
    - Hamilton, James, 6347CY: Burning Oil Well at Night, Near Titusville, Pennsylvania, 1998-1999, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 117)
    - Hammer, Hans Jorgen, 2187CY: In the Cellar, Autumn, 1987, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 118)
    - Hansen, Armin Carl, 5015CY: Still Life With Ginger Jar and Two Pears, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 119)
    - Harari, Hananiah, 2547RY: Into the Past, 1988-2004 (Box 24, Folder 120)
    - Harari, Hananiah, 2548RY: Smiles, 1988-2004 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Harari, Hananiah, 2654CY: Railroad Signals, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Harari, Hananiah, 3649CY: Lavender and Lace, 1992, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Harari, Hananiah, 4886CY: Collage Study for "Smiles", 1996, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Hardy, James, 4196LY: Waiting For Master, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Hare, William, 2520CY: D. Chase Master in Chesapeake Bay/Israel H. Day of Providence, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Harnett, William Michael, 1790CY: Still Life: Box of Havana Cigars, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Harnett, William Michael, 2543JY: Still Life for William Ignatius Blemly, 1988, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Harnett, William Michael, 3597CY: Still Life, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Harnett, William Michael, 3607CY: A Bachelor's Friend, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Harnett, William Michael, 4084CY: Still Life With Three Castles Tobacco #2, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Harnett, William Michael, 6019RY: Still Life With Blue Tobacco Box, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Harnett, William Michael, 6114RY: Still Life With Letter, Inkwell, Coins and a Book, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Harnett, William Michael, 6115RY: Still Life With Tankard, Cheese and Pipe, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Harris and Co., Boston, MA, 4416CY: Weathervane: Leaping Stag, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Harrison, Birge, 1118CY: Egrets on a Sandy Pit, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Harrison, Henry, 4489CY: Afternoon With Grandmother, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Harry, Philip, 2657CY: Lowell's Custom House, Kennebec Road, Maine, 1989-1998 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Hart, James McDougal, 150CY: Landscape With Cattle, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Hart, James McDougal, 221CY: Crossing the River, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Hart, James McDougal, 2818CY: Summer, 1989, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Hart, James McDougal, 3590CY: Adirondack Landscape, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Hart, James McDougal, 3634CY: Adirondack Lake, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Hart, James McDougal, 3799CY: Indian Summer, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Hart, James McDougal, 4480CY: In the Stream, Midsummer, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Hart, James McDougal, 6030CY: New Hampshire, Landscape, 1997, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Hart, James McDougal, 6031CY: Presidential Range, White Mountains, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Hart, William, 191CY: Autumn on the Hudson, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Hart, William, 227CY: Sunlight and Shadow, 1981-1985 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Hart, William, 257CY: Landscape With Cows, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Hart, William, 1332CY: The Watering Place, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Hart, William, 1499CY: Nahant, Near Boston, 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Hart, William, 1533CY: Landscape 1885, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Hart, William, 1872CY: Maine Coast, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Hart, William, 2301CY: Cows in a Landscape, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Hart, William, 2545CY: Breaking Clouds, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Hart, William, 2554RY: Late Summer, 1988, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Hart, William, 2619CY: In the Foothills, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Hart, William, 9005RY: The Land, Keene Valley, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 809CY: Still Life, No. 9, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 998RY: Rio Grande River 1918, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 1346CY: Shoeshone Valley, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 1775CY: Drawing #9, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 1853JY: Three Flowers in a Vase, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 1880CY: Paysage Montagne, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 2002CY: Still Life, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 2661RY: Autumn Cascade I, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 2662RY: Autumn Cascade II, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 2564CY: Still Life With Blue Bowl, 1988-1990 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 4337CY: Flower, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 4498CY: A Lady in Laughter, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 4499CY: New Mexico Recollections #7, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 4614CY: Red Camelias in a Vase, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 4615CY: Dogtown, 1995, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 4779CY: Calla Lilies, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 5047CY: New Mexico Recollections, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 5068CY: Mont Sainte-Victoire, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 5069CY: Woods, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 7436CY: Rio Grande River, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 7524CY: The Mountain of the North, 2000-2004 (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 7561RY: Ear of Corn, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 8994CY: Cyclamen, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 9253CY: Finnish Yankee Wrestler, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Hartman, Bertram, 1201CY: Lady With a Red Umbrella, 1984, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Hartman, Rosella, 3268RY: Books and Irises, 1991, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Hartman, Rosella, 3269RY: Bananas and Grapes, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Hartwick, Gunther, 2246CY: Fishing, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - Hartwick, Gunther, 4766RY: View on the Hudson River, 1996-2002 (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - Harvey, George, 1121CY: Buffalo Hunt, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - Harvey, George, Jr., 1576CY: The Bubble, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 672CY: Roman Campagna, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 1089RY: Sunset Glow, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 72)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 1455CY: Ruins at Taormina by Moonlight, 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 1560CY: The Coast at Nahant, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 74)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 1913CY: Sunset Glow, 1987-1995 (Box 25, Folder 75)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 2794CY: Study for Mt. Etna From Taormina, 1989, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 76)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 2797LY: Mt. Etna From Taormina, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 77)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 2808CY: Porto Venere, Spezia, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 78)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 2893LY: Mt. Etna From Taormina, circa 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 79)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 3397CY: Mt. Etna From Taormina, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 80)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 3428CY: Indian Rock, Narragansett, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 81)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 3574CY: The Lagoon at Venice, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 82)
    - Haseltine, William Stanley, 4376CY: Off Newport, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 83)
    - Haskell, Ernest, 272aRY: Man With Moustache, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 84)
    - Haskell, Ernest, 272bRY: Profile of Christian Brinton, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 85)
    - Haskell, Ernest, 272cRY: Woman in a Hat, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 86)
    - Haskell, Ernest, 272dRY: Man Looking Down, 1981-1989 (Box 25, Folder 87)
    - Haskell, Ernest, 272eRY: Portrait of a Woman, 1981-1989 (Box 25, Folder 88)
    - Haskell, Ernest, 272fRY: Young Woman With Earrings, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 89)
    - Haskell, Ernest, 272gRY: Portrait of an Older Woman, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 90)
    - Haskell, Ernest, 272hRY: Beatrix Briels, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 91)
    - Hassam, Childe: Washington's Birthday, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 92)
    - Hassam, Childe, 103CY: Courtyard in Toledo, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 93)
    - Hassam, Childe, 167CY: Coastal Scene, Spain, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 94)
    - Hassam, Childe, 777RY: Isles of Shoals, Appledore, Maine, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 95)
    - Hassam, Childe, 989CY: Moonlit Sea, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 96)
    - Hassam, Childe, 1007CY: Connecticut Landscape, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 97)
    - Hassam, Childe, 1384CY: On the Beach at Broadstairs, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Hassam, Childe, 1406CY: Mrs. Hassam in the Garden, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Hassam, Childe, 1425CY: Snowy Winter of 1918, Central Park, 1980-1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Hassam, Childe, 1548CY: From the Doorway, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Hassam, Childe, 1709CY: Acorn Street, Boston July 1919, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Hassam, Childe, 2049CY [2040CY?]: A New Year's Nocturne, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Hassam, Childe, 2156CY: Incoming Tide, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Hassam, Childe, 3291CY: Fifth Avenue, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Hassam, Childe, 3578RY: Appledore, Isles of Shoals, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Hassam, Childe, 4127CY: The Rose Garden, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Hassam, Childe, 4339CY: A New Year's Nocturne, New York, 1994, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Hassam, Childe, 4367CY: View on the Thames, London, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Hassam, Childe, 4482CY: Gloucester Harbor, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Hassam, Childe, 4563CY: Cathedral Spires, Spring Morning, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Hassam, Childe, 6837CY: Lady in a Garden, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Hauser, John, 285CY: Indians on Burros, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Hauser, John, 1537CY: Sioux Indian Campsite, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Hawthorne, Charles Webster, 298CY: Satin Skirt, 1981-1982, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Hawthorne, Charles Webster, 464CY: St. Augustine, Florida, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Hawthorne, Charles Webster, 465CY: Court of Oranges, Seville, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Hawthorne, Charles Webster, 602CY: Summer Afternoon on the Beach, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Hawthorne, Charles Webster, 4133CY: Rose, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Hawthorne, Charles Webster, 7463CY: June, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Hays, William Jacob, 895JY: Hanging Woodcocks, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 211CY: Newburyport, Massachusetts, 1981-1984 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 690CY: A Placid Bay, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 1970CY: Sunset Over the Marsh, 1987, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 1492CY: Seacoast Sunset, 1985-1993 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 1579CY: Roses Lying on Gold Velvet, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 1873CY: Jacqueminor Roses, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 2338LY: Hummingbirds, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 3033CY: Decorated Vase with Three Roses, 1990-1996 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 3401CY: Haystacks and Cattle at Sunset, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 3438CY: Still Life with Wine Glass, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 3469CY: Haystacks and Cattle at Sunset, 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 3817CY: Marsh Scene, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 4731CY: Roses in a Victorian Vase, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 6023CY: Pink Orchid and Hummingbirds, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 6351CY: Passion Flowers with Nesting Hummingbirds, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 7534RY: Sun Breaking Through the Clouds, A Wreck on the Shore, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 7611CY: Boston Harbor, 2000-2002 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Healy, George Peter Alexander, 6580CY: Self Portrait, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Held, John, Jr., 1554CY: The Wicker Rocking Chair, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Heller, Helen West, 8485CY: Skating Party, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Hennessy, William John, 2452CY: Springtime, Calvados, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Hennings, E. Martin, 4503CY: In Santa Fe Canyon, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Henri, Robert, 1292CY (old inventory number): Gypsy Boy, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Henri, Robert, 1444CY (new inventory number): Gypsy Boy, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Henri, Robert, 1447CY: Figures in a Spring Landscape, 1981-1985 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Henri, Robert, 1997CY: Gypsy Boy, 1987, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Henri, Robert, 2914CY: Portrait of Carl, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Henri, Robert, 3015CY: Autumn Red and Evergreen, 1990, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Henri, Robert, 3935CY: Le Soledad, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Henri, Robert, 3952CY: Irish Lass, 1988, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Henri, Robert, 4444CY: O in Persian Costume, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Henri, Robert, 4827CY: The Red Flower, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Henri, Robert, 4871CY: The Storm - A Rue in Paris, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Henri, Robert, 6027CY: Viv in Blue Stripe, 1997-1998, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Henri, Robert, 6097CY: The Red Flower, 1997-1999 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Henri, Robert, 6108CY: The Arched Bridge, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Henri, Robert, 7461CY: Winter, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Henri, Robert, 8170JY: The Red Flower, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Henry, Edward Lamson, 115CY: In the Valley, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Henry, Edward Lamson, 166CY: Esopus Canal, 1981, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - Henry, Edward Lamson, 1411CY: Wynwyc, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Henry, Edward Lamson, 1772CY: A Moment of Peril, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - Henry, Edward Lamson, 2698RY: Mother and Child Under a Rose Trellis, 1987-1994 (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Henry, Edward Lamson, 2699RY: Watching Mother Embroider, 1990, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - Henry, Edward Lamson, 2931CY: Façade of Cathedral Piacenza, Lombardy, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 69)
    - Henry, Edward Lamson, 4504CY: The Huckster, 1995, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 70)
    - Henry, Edward Lamson, 7544CY: Horse and Wagon at a Hitching Post, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Herter, Albert, 7038JY: The Prince's Garden, 1999, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 72)
    - Herter Brothers, 3708RY: Library Table, 1992, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Herter Brothers (Attributed), 3835CY: Pair Ebonized Cherry Side Chairs, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - Herter Brothers, 3968CY: Library Table, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 75)
    - Herter Brothers, 4077RY: Partner's Desk, 1993-1997 (Box 26, Folder 76)
    - Herzinger, E., 4357CY: Indians and Redcoats, 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 77)
    - Herzog, Herman, 111CY: Forest Scene with Deer, 1981-1984 (Box 26, Folder 78)
    - Herzog, Herman, 1074CY: Fishing for Supper, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 79)
    - Herzog, Herman, 1373CY: Forest Scene with Deer, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 80)
    - Herzog, Herman, 1501CY: Moonrise, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 81)
    - Herzog, Herman, 2648CY: European Landscape, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 82)
    - Herzog, Herman, 3413LY: Fishing for Supper, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 83)
    - Herzog, Herman, 3679CY: Country Cabin: Summer, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 84)
    - Herzog, Herman, 3680CY: Country Cabin: Autumn, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 85)
    - Herzog, Herman, 3785CY: Daybreak on Snowy Morning, 1992-1995 (Box 26, Folder 86)
    - Herzog, Herman, 4536CY: High in the Rockies, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 87)
    - Herzog, Herman, 4908CY: Forest Scene with Deer, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 88)
    - Herzog, Herman, 7131CY: Sketching on Beaver Creek, 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 89)
    - Herzog, Herman, 7442CY: Country Cabin, Autumn, 2000, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 90)
    - Herzog, Herman, 7443CY: Country Cabin: Summer, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 91)
    - Hetzel, George, 3370CY: Still Life: Grapes, Peaches and Melon, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 92)
    - Hetzel, George, 3516CY: Still Life, 1992, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 93)
    - Hetzel, George (Attributed), 4429CY: Still Life of Watermelon, 1995, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 94)
    - Hewes, Horace G., 4091RY: Chrysanthemums, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 95)
    - Hewit, Mabel A., 3211CY: Provincetown Backyards, 1991-1994 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Hewit, Mabel A., 3212CY: Coal Carriers (No. 2), 1991, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Hewitt, Edwin Hawley, 7114CY: The Singer Building (Pair), 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Hibbard, Aldro Thompson, 2776CY: Early Snow, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Hicks, Edward, 6865RY: Peaceable Kingdom, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Hicks, Edward, 8383CY: Peaceable Kingdom, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Hicks, James Milnor, 7146RY: Trompe L'Oeil With Dollar Bill, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Hicks, Thomas, 1819CY: Ostego Lake, Looking South, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Higgins, Eugene, 1194CY: Fire at the Paris Open, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Higgins, Eugene, 1215CY: War Wagon, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Higgins, Eugene, 7085CY: Pueblo Indian Dancing, 1999, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Hildebrandt, Howard L., 3820CY: Bringing Home the Christmas Tree, 1993, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Hiler, Hilaire, 2344RY: Café Brasserie du Dame, circa 1930s, 1988, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Hiler, Hilaire, 4713JY: Portrait of Sargent Johnson, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Hiler, Hilaire, 4740JY (VOID): Portrait of Sargent Johnson/Mother and Child Porch Sitters, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Hill, Arthur, 4824CY: Cloud Shadows, 1996, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Hill, John Henry, 289RY: Coastal Scene, 1981-1985 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Hill, John Henry, 1956RY: Country Road, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Hill, John Henry, 2151RY: A View of Irvington-on-Hudson, 1987-1988, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 19)